asianbite.com 2007-06-24

# Privacy Policy

Information Collected/Tracked by asianbite 

Information not Directly Submitted by Users to asianbite 

This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site. 

Use of Information Obtained by asianbite

Information that users do not submit to us 

We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website. 

Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

As a matter of policy, except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. However, asianbite may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to members more targeted advertising, products and services. In such situations we will never disclose information that will be used to personally identify you. 

Links

This site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that asianbite is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Use of Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Cookies are used to manage sessions on our site. Users must enable cookies to use our site. Also, users may optionally use a cookie to remember their password in order to automatically log in to our site. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user which they did not intentionally submit to us. 

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

asianbite users may modify their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile. 

Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Security

Your asianbite account is password-protected. This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. We limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us. 

Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. asianbite does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.
